What causes income inequality?
- Maybe I should narrow it down to the United States. 
- Inequality of oppurtunity
	- Education
		- number of junior high and high schools
		- number of universities
	- firms
		- number of top/rich firms 
	- tax
		- standards of paying taxes?
	- economy
		- inflation
	- Idea
		- distance to the sea from the capital city, number of big cities, estimated population, average temperature, SAT scores / number of applicatns / physical appearance, carbon emission, the amount of carbon that has been emitted per capita